question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "King Gizzard &amp; The Lizard Wizard&#039;s album &quot;Nonagon Infinity&quot; can be looped seamlessly.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Did Michael Jackson invent the moonwalk?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "March 10th is also known as Mar10 Day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge", "question": "Is a dog a mammal?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
